Girtonia   Dark Forest, Defensive Line
Saint Heal.
The pain's gone!
Take care now.
Excellent work.
On top of maintaining our barrier,
you heal our injured...
I'm sorry to keep asking so much of you.
Not at all.
You and your team do the lion's share
of the monster slaying.
Uggggh...
I got so sick of bailing
my old guard out all the time...
I actually appreciate having the flexibility.
More than anything...
Aunt Hilde's return to saintly
duties has been a lifesaver.
If not for dividing the kingdom with her,
both the land and I would
be in tatters right now.
But even then...
We've only bought ourselves a few days.
The barrier Philia erected shattered today.
My shadow...
Bring Saint Philia
to me!
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Episode 8
"With You, Who Gave Me Courage"
Saint Bind.
Who are you?
First time seeing a demon?
It's a pleasure to meet you,
Miss Greatest of All Time.
My name is Erza Notice.
I'm an exorcist.
An exorcist?
The demon hunters from the Church of Cremoux?
You're as smart as they say.
I came to warn you about the
approach of the Demon Realm
that happens every few centuries.
But I wasn't expecting him to have
strengthened enough to send his shadow.
Do you mean the archdemon Asmodeus?
Oh? You know about that, too?
If the power of the Demon Realm
continues to wax,
the sealed archdemon, Asmodeus,
will revive for sure.
And his first target...
will be you, Saint Philia.
I have an in-name-only national
defense meeting coming up.
Maybe I'll check on
Prince Fernand beforehand.
I was so busy yesterday hunting
monsters and reforming the barrier,
I didn't have time to try
persuading him again...
Saint Mia?
Where might you be off to?
That's not the way to the conference room.
Marquis Pyrz?
A supporter of Prince Julius's.
The strongest backer of the
second prince faction, even.
I've heard word that you've been
frequenting Prince Fernand's villa.
What kind of behavior is that
for an affianced girl?
My fiancé's brother is in poor health.
What kind of saint would I be
if I showed no concern for him?
I also thought it might help
to improve my healing techniques,
so I took it upon myself
to pay him a house call.
But he turns me away
every time, I'm afraid...
Oh, is that all it is?
What a beneficent saint we have.
He's clearly relieved to hear that.
However, it would be best
for you to leave him be.
It's his choice to be housebound, after all.
It's the way you've treated him
that made him close his heart off so!
It's time.
Let's go to the conference room.
Wh...
What?!
What are you doing here, Fernand?!
Watch your tongue, Julius.
You should show your
elder brother more respect.
Why, after he was so determined
not to leave his room...?
I'm delighted to see you in good spirits.
But shouldn't you be in bed right now?
It's not good for your health
to overexert yourself.
That's true. I hope he can take this.
I appreciate your concern.
But I'm feeling quite well at the moment.
With our father taken ill,
it's important that I step in...
as the crown prince.
Prince Fernand! Isn't that too far a step?
You don't know what he might
try if you provoke him!
This is what I want.
To force my brother to make a move.
Really, I can't believe you unilaterally
refused Parnacorta's aid.
Their king is an old friend of our father's.
Our kingdoms are allies, so—
Never mind that!
It's obvious they have an ulterior motive
in sending their knights here!
They want to capitalize
on the chaos and take us over!
What?
A kingdom about to be ravaged by monsters?
That'd be a funny thing to take over.
I thought he'd be more
afraid of Prince Julius,
but he's handling himself well.
No... he's putting on a front.
Of course he hasn't recovered this quickly.
Trauma doesn't disappear overnight either.
But he's still rising to the occasion.
In that case, as the one who spurred him
to this, I need to support him!
I won't let the one fighting
on the front line get hurt!
Brother, that's a ridiculous argument.
And then there's Philia!
The fact that she refused my demand for
her return shows she's working for them now!
What kind of unfeeling woman refuses
to aid her homeland in its hour of need?!
She's a traitor!
We should arrest her for treason!
Oh no! Mia's exceeded her anger
limit and gone completely blank!
Goodness gracious.
It should have been obvious
Parnacorta would never accept.
Let's stop with these childish tantrums
and discuss a few more constructive ideas—
You be quiet, Brother!
All right! Our first duty is to strip
Marquess Adenauer of his assets and title!
The parents of the traitor must be punished!
This conference is hereby over!
You're all dismissed!
I'm sorry. That's the best I could do for now.
The medicine's worn off.
Inconvenient, I know.
Not at all.
You did wonderfully, Your Highness!
You deserve a nice, long rest.
Thank you so much for being brave.
You were really very dashing back there!
Was I? It was worth making the trip, then.
But Mia, please be careful.
You're confiscating our assets?!
Y-You can't do that!
You have no good reason—
If you wish to avoid it,
then assist me with my plan!
My provocation will incite
my brother to action.
We need to use this opportunity
to expose him for what he is.
Yes, this is the critical moment.
So let's make it official, Your Highness.
Will you fight with me?
Of course.
With you, who gave me courage.
You're...
Former Saint Hildegarde.
There's something I need to discuss with you.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Kingdom of Bolmern  Mattilas Estate
What?!
You want me to help expand the
Great Purification Circle?
You expect me to play second
fiddle to the likes of Philia Adenauer?!
Yes, Big Sister Emily.
Eldest Daughter of the Mattilas Family
Emily Mattilas
I've already discussed the plan with Father.
He was overjoyed and ran right off
to get the king's permission.
Sounds great!
Now you've got Father playing messenger
boy for the kingdom next door?
This is utter madness!
Not to mention...
This is all for the likes of Philia Adenauer?!
I had a feeling this would happen.
Big Sister Emily sees Philia,
the greatest saint of all time, as her rival.
Besides, our efforts alone have
been enough to keep Bolmern safe!
As the eldest daughter
of the Mattilas family, I say we—
Okay, that's enough.
Big Sister Emily,
Third Daughter of the Mattilas Family
Jane Mattilas
Second Daughter of the Mattilas Family
Amanda Mattilas
the monster threat will only worsen.
As bright as you are, I'm sure you know that.
URK
Well, I...
I think Big Sister Emily is jealous of Philia!
Though that would hardly
be becoming of a saint.
Jane, y-you be quiet!
I am most certainly not
given to such petty feelings!
I just have to do it, don't I?
It's my duty as a saint, I suppose!
I'm glad it all worked out.
Don't get the wrong idea!
I barely think about Philia Adenauer!
Thank you so much, Big Sister Jane!
Now, what would you like us to do?
To expand the Great Purification Circle,
we need an ancient ritual
called a magic-convergence spell.
First, I'll teach you the
fundamentals of ancient rituals.
Here is the manual
Saint Philia prepared for us.
To begin, we should practice mana perception
with a spell called Robe of Light.
Let's see...
So it goes like... this?
Come, light...
She mastered the Robe of Light instantly?
C-Clear proof of my inborn talent!
I certainly don't owe it to Philia Adenauer!
This...
What in the world is this?
It's incredible.
This is too great a gift.
We'd shame the Mattilas family
to remain so deeply in her debt!
Amanda! Jane!
Let's learn this magic-convergence
spell as quickly as possible!
We'll show them what
the saints of Bolmern can do!
Let's do it!
Everything's going to work out!
Saint Mia!
Prince Julius is making his move.
I wasn't expecting Prince Fernand's
provocation to work so quickly.
This is absurdly rash for the
supposed leader of a kingdom, isn't it?
Though that's to our benefit this time.
What has he done?
He's ordered House Adenauer
to throw a large party.
A party?!
Now is when we nobles must band together!
And he's invited most of the noble families.
I can't follow that man's logic at all!
Saint Mia!
Thank goodness. I was waiting for you.
What is it?
Well, you see...
A man came in for confession,
and he insists that you be the one to hear it.
The son of Marquis Pyrz
from the second prince faction!
I hope you'll forgive my intrusion.
The truth is... there's something
I wanted to tell you.
What an exhausting day...
What in the world?!
Nobody called for you!
What's all the racket?
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing here?
You're not welcome here, Hildegarde!
Auntie?!
It's unbecoming for the head
of a household to shout like that.
I've come to share information
with Mia, as a fellow saint.
I'll leave the moment I'm finished.
Then do it and get out already!
Some saint you are, at your age...
It's a bit noisy here.
Care to join me outside?
O-Of course.
I haven't seen her in so long...
She and Big Sister Philia
really do look alike!
No, knock it off!
I'm so grateful you've resumed
your saintly duties, Auntie.
Thanks to you, we've managed
to halt the monsters' advance.
No need to flatter me.
My return is but a drop in the ocean.
This kingdom is on the verge
of falling to the monsters.
A truly deplorable state of affairs.
My pupil, Philia, could have
solved this entirely on her own...
That's true.
We're only slowing them down.
We haven't done anything real.
Well then, Auntie...
What did you want to discuss?
Allow me to get right to the point.
Mia, will you let me adopt you?
What?
Sooner or later, your parents
will meet their ruin.
Your revenge is going to condemn them
as surely as it does Prince Julius.
She knows about that?
I am part of the crown prince faction.
Prince Julius sold away my precious pupil.
How could I ever forgive him?
Pierre told me that you'd joined our side,
so I've waited for a chance to talk with you.
You're sure to struggle
after losing your parents.
I have also lost my husband,
but I'm sure I can find a way to support you.
But...
You barely even know me.
Why would you adopt me?
What does that matter?
Your parents already stole my daughter.
No...
You can't mean...
Would you like to hear an old story?
My younger brother—
your father, Marquis Adenauer—
was jealous of the attention our
mother gave me, as a future saint.
In time, he came to resent and despise me.
He began to spread malicious lies about me,
and by the time our mother passed,
everyone around us had come
to believe his lies.
Though I was a saint,
I was driven from our home
and lost my standing as a
member of House Adenauer.
My younger brother, then poised
to carry on the family line, got married,
but they failed to bear a child.
As the head of a family of saints, it was
imperative that he produce a daughter.
And so they set their eyes on Philia,
with whom I was pregnant at the time.
If it's a girl, I'll use her!
When he learned she was a girl,
he stole her from me
and spread rumors that my baby was stillborn.
When I told people Philia was my daughter,
they thought I'd simply gone mad
with grief from losing my child.
Soon after, my husband who'd recently
fallen ill took a turn for the worse.
And so I lost him as well.
Brokenhearted, I lost
the will to fight altogether.
In the end, the only
thing I could do for her
was ensure she was strong enough
to stand on her own.
After all, for letting her go
in the first place,
I am unworthy to call myself a mother.
I have no intention of telling her.
But... then why did you tell me?
Why?!
I'm their real daughter!
Why would you tell me that?!
The reason is simple.
This is my own revenge.
It worked, then.
Because, as awful as they've been,
I felt they had to have
some goodness in them.
But now, what little hope I clung
to has been completely wiped away.
Moreover, because those awful people
eventually had a daughter of their own...
That means I'm the reason they
treated my sister so awfully!
I'm so sorry, Philia!
I have no right to call myself your sister!
If what you say is true,
this makes even less sense.
Why would you adopt your
beloathed brother's daughter?
I received a letter from Parnacorta.
It was from Philia.
She wrote at great length
of how worried she is for you.
Please, help the current saint,
Mia, however you can.
She's very kind, and also very strong.
She puts all her heart
into anything she tries
and sometimes pushes herself too hard,
so I'm worried about her.
Mia is my younger sister.
Unlike me, she's a very good girl.
I love her very much.
When my engagement
to Prince Julius was decided
and I was called back to House Adenauer,
I felt no connection whatsoever to that place,
which should have felt like home.
But Mia welcomed me so warmly.
Welcome home!
I believe it only became my home
because she was there.
I didn't realize I felt that way at the time.
But having learned in Parnacorta
to look back on my life with clarity,
I think I can see now...
that Mia's kindness has saved me.
I believe Girtonia needs the light she shines.
So I ask of you, my mentor...
Please be there for Mia.
The Too-Perfect Saint Tossed Aside by
My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom.
Next time, episode 9:
Next Time
Episode 9
"Crossroads of Fate"
"Crossroads of Fate."